Chatswood, NSW 2067 +61 431 459 638

www.github.com/victorzottmann

Victor Zottmann

zottmann.victor@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vzottmann

Frontend Developer

www.victorzottmann.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated frontend developer with 1.5 years of experience and a multidisciplinary background. With a keen eye for design, Victor seeks to acquire further frontend skills to enhance interactions and elevate user experiences, while also exploring related disciplines to broaden his expertise in web development.

SKILLS

Technical Skills:

- Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Bootstrap, Git / GitHub
- Familiar with CSS-in-JS, SASS, REST APIs, TypeScript, Bash, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Unit Testing, Jira, Confluence

Soft Skills

 Teamwork, Positive Attitude, Problem-Solving, Strong Communication, Strong Work Ethic, Adaptability, Creative and Critical Thinking, Time Management

EMPLOYMENT

Engineering Intern Audinate Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- Streamlined development processes by successfully replacing a deprecated API responsible for file storage management within the company's database system using React, MongoDB, and Node.js.
- · Wrote unit tests in the Mocha testing framework to ensure data integrity when uploading and downloading files.

Engineering Intern Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

- Enhanced the accessibility of an internal customer support platform by integrating multi-language support using the React Intl and React Context APIs with TypeScript.
- Designed wireframes to aid engineers in improving the usability of the customer support platform.
- Helped product owners and managers refine customer requirements by developing practical user stories.

Research and Development Intern

Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

- In collaboration with an external client, participated in comprehensive testing of a proprietary desktop application, ensuring its smooth and successful release to market.
- Played an integral role in the design thinking process and wireframe prototyping of a new product, contributing valuable insights to its development.

Junior Contributor DesigningSound.org Jun 2018 - Jan 2019

https://designingsound.org/author/victor

· Published several articles, tutorials, interviews, reviews, and studies on the art and technique of sound design.

Correspondent Jun 2017 - Jun 2018

· Was promoted to Junior Contributor in June 2018 due to the quality and outreach of the contributions.

Sound Designer Ignition Immersive May 2017 - Nov 2017

- · Created immersive sound design for virtual reality experiences using spatial audio techniques.
- · Developed project management and technical solutions to facilitate a robust workflow to the audio team.

EDUCATION

Sydney, NSW University of Technology Sydney Feb 2022 - Dec 2023

Master of Interaction Design (Extension) - GPA: 6.44 / 7

- Major: Interaction Programming
- Awards: Dean's List Engineering 2023, LATAM International Postgraduate Coursework Scholarship